let savollar23 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to advance",
        answer: "A. oldinga yurmoq",
        options: [
            "A. oldinga yurmoq",
            "B. orqaga qaytmoq",
            "C. to'xtamoq",
            "D. qaytmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "athlete",
        answer: "B. sportchi",
        options: [
            "A. o'qituvchi",
            "B. sportchi",
            "C. musiqachi",
            "D. san'atkor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "average",
        answer: "C. o'rtacha",
        options: [
            "A. kambag'al",
            "B. boy",
            "C. o'rtacha",
            "D. g'ayrioddiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "behavior",
        answer: "A. xulq-atvor",
        options: [
            "A. xulq-atvor",
            "B. ko'rinish",
            "C. bilim",
            "D. sog'liq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "behind",
        answer: "D. orqasida",
        options: [
            "A. oldida",
            "B. yonida",
            "C. ustida",
            "D. orqasida"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "course",
        answer: "B. dars",
        options: [
            "A. imtihon",
            "B. dars",
            "C. tanaffus",
            "D. yil"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to lower",
        answer: "A. pasay(tir)moq",
        options: [
            "A. pasay(tir)moq",
            "B. ko'tarmoq",
            "C. saqlamoq",
            "D. yo'qotmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "to match",
        answer: "B. mos kelmoq",
        options: [
            "A. aralashtirmoq",
            "B. mos kelmoq",
            "C. yo'q qilmoq",
            "D. ajratmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "member",
        answer: "C. a'zo",
        options: [
            "A. rahbar",
            "B. tomoshabin",
            "C. a'zo",
            "D. raqib"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "mental",
        answer: "A. aqliy",
        options: [
            "A. aqliy",
            "B. jismoniy",
            "C. hissiy",
            "D. fizikalik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "passenger",
        answer: "B. yo'lovchi",
        options: [
            "A. haydovchi",
            "B. yo'lovchi",
            "C. politsiyachi",
            "D. uchuvchi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "personality",
        answer: "D. shaxsiyat",
        options: [
            "A. ism",
            "B. yosh",
            "C. kasb",
            "D. shaxsiyat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "poem",
        answer: "A. she'r",
        options: [
            "A. she'r",
            "B. roman",
            "C. maqola",
            "D. eslatma"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "pole",
        answer: "B. ustun",
        options: [
            "A. arqon",
            "B. ustun",
            "C. taxta",
            "D. quti"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to remove",
        answer: "A. olib tashlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. olib tashlamoq",
            "B. qo'shmoq",
            "C. saqlamoq",
            "D. o'zgartirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "safety",
        answer: "C. xavfsizlik",
        options: [
            "A. xavf",
            "B. risk",
            "C. xavfsizlik",
            "D. baxtsiz hodisalar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to shoot",
        answer: "A. otmoq",
        options: [
            "A. otmoq",
            "B. uloqtirmoq",
            "C. ushlamoq",
            "D. urmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "to sound",
        answer: "B. ovoz chiqarmoq",
        options: [
            "A. hidlamoq",
            "B. ovoz chiqarmoq",
            "C. tatib ko'rmoq",
            "D. ko'rmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "to swim",
        answer: "A. suzmoq",
        options: [
            "A. suzmoq",
            "B. yugurmoq",
            "C. uchmoq",
            "D. sakramoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "web",
        answer: "C. o'rgimchak to'ri",
        options: [
            "A. ko'cha",
            "B. eshik",
            "C. o'rgimchak to'ri",
            "D. deraza"
        ]
    }
];
